[{"sentence": "The professor conducted an inquiry into the status of the file.", "question": "Did the professor conduct someone/something?", "answer": "Yes", "idan": "Idan_01_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_01_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The commissioner wrote a report for the chairman.", "question": "Did the commissioner write someone/something?", "answer": "Yes", "idan": "Idan_02_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_02_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The terrorist assassinated the newsman in cold blood.", "question": "Did the terrorist kill someone/something?", "answer": "Yes", "idan": "Idan_03_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_03_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "A legislator lied to the consultant about a new bill.", "question": "Did the legislator lie about someone/something?", "answer": "Yes", "idan": "Idan_04_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_04_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The toddler hugged a teddybear because he was scared.", "question": "Did the toddler hug someone/something?", "answer": "Yes", "idan": "Idan_05_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_05_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The spy monitored a baroness for several months.", "question": "Did the spy watch someone/something?", "answer": "Yes", "idan": "Idan_06_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_06_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The witch was hanged by an executioner promptly at dawn.", "question": "Did the executioner hang someone/something?", "answer": "Yes", "idan": "Idan_07_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_07_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The pianist met with a beautician to prepare for her recital.", "question": "Did the pianist meet with someone/something?", "answer": "Yes", "idan": "Idan_08_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_08_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "A socialite was greeted by the butler with a plate of caviar.", "question": "Did the butler greet someone/something?", "answer": "Yes", "idan": "Idan_09_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_09_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The pirate stole the booty from an officer.", "question": "Did the pirate steal someone/something?", "answer": "Yes", "idan": "Idan_10_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_10_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The colonel was knighted by the queen because of his loyalty.", "question": "Did the queen knight someone/something?", "answer": "Yes", "idan": "Idan_11_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_11_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The spokesman toasted a muffin for the agent after the early morning appointment.", "question": "Did the spokesman do something for someone/something?", "answer": "Yes", "idan": "Idan_12_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_12_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The supplier described a scenario for the class after explaining basic concepts.", "question": "Did the supplier explain someone/something?", "answer": "Yes", "idan": "Idan_13_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_13_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "A bystander was rescued by the fireman in the nick of time.", "question": "Did the fireman rescue someone/something?", "answer": "Yes", "idan": "Idan_14_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_14_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The defendant misled a juryman when she said that she worked for the government.", "question": "Was the juryman misled by someone/something?", "answer": "Yes", "idan": "Idan_15_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_15_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The translator found a car for the ambassador because he could not speak Lebanese.", "question": "Was a car found for someone/something?", "answer": "Yes", "idan": "Idan_16_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_16_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The acrobat respected the ballerina because she went to Juilliard.", "question": "Was the ballerina respected by someone/something?", "answer": "Yes", "idan": "Idan_17_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_17_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The principal commended a parent for her ability to motivate her child.", "question": "Was the parent commended by someone/something?", "answer": "Yes", "idan": "Idan_18_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_18_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The robot killed a scientist before escaping from the laboratory.", "question": "Did the robot escape from someone/something?", "answer": "Yes", "idan": "Idan_19_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_19_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The preacher irritated a parishioner because she was used to shorter sermons.", "question": "Was the parishioner irritated by someone/something?", "answer": "Yes", "idan": "Idan_20_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_20_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The presenter was criticized by a legislator because of his speech impediment.", "question": "Did the legislator criticize someone/something?", "answer": "Yes", "idan": "Idan_21_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_21_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "An analyst angered the economist after he interrupted a phone conference five times.", "question": "Was the economist angered by someone/something?", "answer": "Yes", "idan": "Idan_22_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_22_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The advisee opened a file for the visitor with some trepidation.", "question": "Was the file opened by someone/something?", "answer": "Yes", "idan": "Idan_23_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_23_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The choreographer found a film starring the lead in the musical.", "question": "Was the film found by someone/something?", "answer": "Yes", "idan": "Idan_24_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_24_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The playwright selected the understudy because of his resemblance to the lead actor.", "question": "Did the understudy receive someone/something?", "answer": "No", "idan": "Idan_25_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_25_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The insurer paid the victim because his car had been destroyed.", "question": "Did the victim pay someone/something?", "answer": "No", "idan": "Idan_26_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_26_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The runner filled a bottle with cold tap water.", "question": "Did the runner receive someone/something?", "answer": "No", "idan": "Idan_27_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_27_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The sculptor brought a shell from the ocean floor.", "question": "Did the shell receive someone/something?", "answer": "No", "idan": "Idan_28_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_28_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The dealer shuffled the deck before distributing the cards.", "question": "Did the cards receive someone/something?", "answer": "No", "idan": "Idan_29_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_29_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The trainer filled a bag with ice for the injured client.", "question": "Did the trainer receive someone/something?", "answer": "No", "idan": "Idan_30_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_30_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The cameraman was paid to follow a bridesmaid down the aisle with his camera.", "question": "Did the cameraman volunteer to film someone/something?", "answer": "No", "idan": "Idan_31_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_31_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The rioter stapled the sign to a bulletin board in the corridor.", "question": "Did the rioter receive someone/something?", "answer": "No", "idan": "Idan_32_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_32_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The paramedic helped an invalid into the brick building", "question": "Did the paramedic receive someone/something?", "answer": "No", "idan": "Idan_33_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_33_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The trucker ordered a bartender to bring him a beer.", "question": "Did the bartender receive someone/something?", "answer": "No", "idan": "Idan_34_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_34_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The performer lifted the acrobat onto her shoulders gracefully.", "question": "Did the acrobat receive someone/something?", "answer": "No", "idan": "Idan_35_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_35_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The archivist found a document dating back to the Nixon administration.", "question": "Did the archivist receive someone/something?", "answer": "No", "idan": "Idan_36_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_36_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The intern begged a programmer to edit the program because it was due the next day.", "question": "Did the intern receive someone/something?", "answer": "No", "idan": "Idan_37_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_37_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The surgeon called for a nurse to assist him with the operation.", "question": "Did the nurse receive someone/something?", "answer": "No", "idan": "Idan_38_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_38_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The beekeeper selected a honeycomb carefully from a hive of swarming bees.", "question": "Did the beekeeper eat someone/something?", "answer": "No", "idan": "Idan_39_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_39_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The Vikings raided a village in search of the warrior.", "question": "Did the warrior receive someone/something?", "answer": "No", "idan": "Idan_40_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_40_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The jewelry-maker was commissioned by the millionaire.", "question": "Did the millionaire receive someone/something?", "answer": "No", "idan": "Idan_41_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_41_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The cheerleader was treated by a doctor who had been watching the game.", "question": "Did the cheerleader call someone/something?", "answer": "No", "idan": "Idan_42_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_42_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The alum was offended by the solicitor because he asked very personal questions.", "question": "Did the alum receive someone/something?", "answer": "No", "idan": "Idan_43_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_43_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The astronaut accepted the mission.", "question": "Did the astronaut receive someone/something?", "answer": "No", "idan": "Idan_44_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_44_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The assistant xeroxed a file for the editor after sorting some papers.", "question": "Did the assistant receive someone/something?", "answer": "No", "idan": "Idan_45_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_45_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The coach encouraged the team to score in the last quarter.", "question": "Did the coach receive someone/something?", "answer": "No", "idan": "Idan_46_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_46_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The butcher cleaned a knife before he sliced the ham.", "question": "Did the butcher receive someone/something?", "answer": "No", "idan": "Idan_47_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_47_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The sergeant assigned a locker to the private after the meeting.", "question": "Did the sergeant receive someone/something?", "answer": "No", "idan": "Idan_48_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_48_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The man held the woman.", "question": "Did the woman hold something/someone?", "answer": "No", "idan": "Idan_49_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_49_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The airplane destroyed the missile.", "question": "Did the missile destroy something/someone?", "answer": "No", "idan": "Idan_50_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_50_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The father chased the son.", "question": "Did the son chase something/someone?", "answer": "No", "idan": "Idan_51_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_51_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The nephew tickled the uncle.", "question": "Did the nephew tickle something/someone?", "answer": "Yes", "idan": "Idan_52_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_52_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The woman nudged the man.", "question": "Did the woman nudge something/someone?", "answer": "Yes", "idan": "Idan_53_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_53_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The daughter bit the son.", "question": "Did the daughter bite something/someone?", "answer": "Yes", "idan": "Idan_54_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_54_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The husband was called by the wife.", "question": "Did the husband call something/someone?", "answer": "No", "idan": "Idan_55_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_55_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The girl was pushed by the boy.", "question": "Did the girl push something/someone?", "answer": "No", "idan": "Idan_56_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_56_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The wife was ignored by the husband.", "question": "Did the wife ignore something/someone?", "answer": "No", "idan": "Idan_57_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_57_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The niece was followed by the aunt.", "question": "Did the aunt follow something/someone?", "answer": "Yes", "idan": "Idan_58_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_58_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The professor was criticized by the TA.", "question": "Did the TA criticize something/someone?", "answer": "Yes", "idan": "Idan_59_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_59_filler_eng.wav"}, {"sentence": "The lawyer was insulted by the judge.", "question": "Did the judge insult something/someone?", "answer": "Yes", "idan": "Idan_60_filler_eng.wav", "nezar": "Nezar_60_filler_eng.wav"}]